hi okay this is my Easter sermon you get
to hear the birds and the bees okay and
then if we'll try to do the last class
okay okay
[Music]
alright then so a good a CI teacher
should have all four legs at the table
okay number one is know your stuff know
your content
number two is know how to teach know how
to present to a group okay number three
good behavior
professional behavior number four yeah
how to organize an event how to pay for
it how to pay your taxes etc
professional behavior to me eighty
percent is money and sex okay
and I'd like to talk about the second
one today and I'm basing this on a DCI
lecture I gave it's called the garden of
hormones and there's images that go
along with this but I think we'll just
keep going it then as a teacher a big
part of professional behaviors how you
act around other the opposite sex how do
men act towards women how do women act
towards men and it's kind of amazing in
the monastery they don't really give
them this lecture and lots of young men
come to Western countries and I brought
I think ape myself I did the green cards
and six of them gave up their vows and I
stopped doing it so it's it's an
important thing to talk about I think if
you're gonna be a teacher we should talk
about it openly and honestly and don't
be too shy okay and
so there is I did send you some no
didn't I send you hang on I gotta send
some to Tim I did send it to you but
okay I think
okay it's ready almost and in America
like you know parents are supposed to
tell their kids about this stuff you
know when the kids are young the parents
tell them there's a special bird that
brings babies and so kids don't know
anything about sex and then when the kid
gets about I don't know thirteen
fourteen the parents are supposed to
give them this lecture you know about
birth control and things like that okay
and the HIV and things like that okay so
here's how I like to teach it Tim now
you have the images I think and I'm
gonna go in order you got the first one
okay
what's interesting is that flowers and
trees also have sex and in the history
of the West when they were studying
about trees how trees have sex
it was monks Christian monks in Europe
who in the Middle Ages who were
discovering about how trees have babies
and flowers in and they made a strange
decision not to use English they use
Latin words and they call plants and
trees by Latin names and all the sex
organs of the flower are called by Latin
names because they were embarrassed they
didn't want anyone to know what they're
talking about but flowers have penis
flowers have vagina
flowers have trees have sperm okay
flowers have over eggs over like in the
word for apple tree is Marlo's Camilla
and so they gave everything Latin names
I think cuz they were a little
embarrassed okay
then as you know this picture is where's
that picture I can't see it is it a
Robin ever okay
the Robin the male I think has the
bright color red color and the female
has a kind of gray color okay and this
color of the birds difference in color
is for mainly for reproduction
okay the boys are trying to look sexy to
the girls okay and because continuing
the Robin Bird lineage is the most
important function of the body you know
so all animals
and all plants they want to make more of
the same kind they don't want their line
to stop they want to keep having babies
and this is the main purpose of a plant
this is the main thing they do you know
everything is connected to trying to
keep themself going as a species okay
apple trees gotta have sex it's not an
option you know and it's the main thing
they do okay and many years ago they
decided to use Latin words in the West I
don't know about China so and this urge
in a living being is as strong as a
nuclear bomb okay every living thing
trees plants birds fish humans the main
subject of the body is to produce more
of the same thing so it's a deep deep
power and it makes you a motorcy ago
what's it mean love is blind this is
from Don Quixote first page
I studied Don Quixote but I only
finished the first page and it's a
thousand pages anything and and
therefore love love is blind because
hormones are blinding ok we will do
anything to have another human and trees
will do anything to have another tree
and flowers will do anything to have
another tree it's a very very strong
power and we all have it
ok so don't think I'm talking about
somebody else I'm talking about you we
all have it all ACI teachers have it ok
and also is there students have it ok
and and it makes you foolish ok
I'm talking I'm the guy who took my ship
crashed into the reef I'm trying to tell
you where the reef is you have the
second ship
then I'm the best helper for you because
I crashed my ship already okay so I can
tell you very very powerful most
powerful emotion in a human being and
people don't know and nobody warns them
you know you have nuclear weapon down
between your legs nobody warned us you
know my parents didn't say then I just
discovered it okay so the main purpose
of life is to create more life and
that's a good thing that's a beautiful
thing without that nuclear force
we won't be here our parents have won't
have made us okay then it's interesting
to study how the parts of a flower you
have that next one yeah this is called
pistol and stamen okay
pistol is the female part of the flower
and the stamen is the male part of the
florist the pistol has the eggs and the
stamen has two sperm okay which we call
pollen in the anther okay and actually a
it's possible for a Florida have sex
with itself the the male part can make
eggs which is pollen and it can drop it
into the female part which is the
entering a pistol and it will have
another flower and that's the main goal
of a flower is to put the semen into the
lady okay humans also okay and that's
why okay you ready don't look so
embarrassed I'm just I'm doing what your
mom and dad should have done
that's why flowers are beautiful colors
okay they're not for beauty they're for
reproduction okay why it's true a flower
can drop semen into the female part of
the flower but that will be like a man
marrying his sister and the blood gets
weaker the bloodline gets meaner with
the genes get weaker so it's better if
the sperm from one flower goes to the
vagina of the other flower it's better
now you know why flowers are so
beautiful why they're trying to attract
the bee next photo okay and these have
these combs on their legs and when they
walk through the flower they just want
the nectar okay there's a tasty juice in
the flower similar to the perfume that
lady's worth okay and the Beave just
wants the juice but by accident he will
get sperm on his pollen on his legs okay
and that's all a big plan by god I don't
know who okay so they just came for to
have a margarita and when they left the
flower their leg is covered with
somebody else's sperm okay then they fly
to the other flower and the pollen drops
off okay
and that's why flowers are beautiful
that's the only reason okay Buddha
didn't make flowers for you he made it
to have babies okay so the flower is
trying to attract the bee to get the
stuff on his legs so he can spread it to
another flower and make the line
stronger crossbreeding we call
crossbreeding so it would be stronger I
have in my yard mulberry tree when you
call came from China it's the tree that
silkworm seen so it's very famous and
there's male trees and female trees
I believe the female tree has been
banned in Phoenix it's illegal to sell a
female mulberry tree because they make a
mess with the berries okay and that's
another story okay then the flower gets
what you call pregnant okay and you can
use the same words
it's just monks who changed it five
hundred years ago they didn't want to
use the straight language but the flower
gets pregnant and then it it grows into
a fruit okay that the petals drop off we
don't need the color anymore we already
got pregnant it's like when your life
your wife start stops wearing miniskirts
after she's six months pregnant because
we already the miniskirt already worked
okay and she got pregnant now she
doesn't need the flower anymore okay and
then the fruit will grow and what's
amazing is inside the fruit next photo
is that watermelon is it a watermelon
yeah there's a thousand new seeds in one
pregnant lady so better it's not twins
or triplets it's one thousand babies in
there okay and each one has power to
make a thousand babies you see so it's
very powerful and the flower will drop
off even with a rose you'll get rose
hips and they will produce seeds and
those will become the next generation of
rose okay
and it's interesting when you grow roses
if you want them to be healthy as soon
as they get old you cut them off because
the plant will put all its energy into
making new seats
trying to get new pregnant okay if you
cut the Rose off the old one the plants
like oh no my baby abortion I need
another flower and then the plant will
make another flower to try to bring
another beat and this desire to repeat
the species to keep the species going is
the strongest instinct in in plants okay
[Music]
and the fruits any kind of food like
watermelon fruit the watermelon that you
eat this is milk for the baby okay this
is the same as milk for the baby it's
supposed to if you want to have fun you
know grow some watermelons and don't
pick them and they will spoil and then
those seeds will sit in the old milk and
they will grow very strong and you will
have a hundred more watermelons next
year okay it's very interesting fruits
are the purpose of fruit is to feed the
baby okay you are stealing baby's food
when you eat watermelon shaquan okay
then the next sentence in the essay says
why are we talking about plant flower
sex in the middle of a CI teacher
training I'm getting there okay
next picture
supposed to be a beautiful lady I don't
know there we go
ladies do the same thing as flowers okay
and this picture has both okay so so at
a young age women are taught by their
culture
oh you must buy makeup you must be
beautiful you must wear attractive
clothes and that's been going on for
50,000 years
you see everybody for God why you you
know you don't think about it but your
family your country your history your
culture tells you dress fancy put on
makeup you know look like a flower
why yeah
we need a bee okay and that's been
thousands of years and it's all hormones
okay it's not fashion it's not beauty
it's we need a bee okay to be honest I
enjoy fashion as you guys know I really
like it but to be honest the original
reason for fancy clothes makeup boys
also because the the bright colored
birds are the boys okay
it's to attract the girl also and and
you don't even know your culture
designed it that way you we forgot okay
you don't even know what's going on you
just do it okay oh the TV says I need
this kind of lipstick I'll buy this kind
of our by Lancome you know at the whole
history of your culture for 50 thousand
years is brainwashing you you know young
women if they don't wear makeup if they
don't really nice clothes there are bad
people there are not nice people you
know they are lazy or Veronica told me
her mom wouldn't let them go out of the
without lipstick she had three sisters
for sister total still the mothers 94 we
still visit her and she's laying on the
bed she'll say writing it did you put on
your lipstick okay don't tell Veronica I
say okay and the whole purpose of all
that is it's not mainly for beauty and
it's not mainly for fashion it's to
attract bees okay why we need more
people okay if if everyone stops having
babies
we will stop human race was thought so
it's a very very powerful energy in
every human being I have to make a bit I
must make a baby okay so there's a
difference between men and women
okay the bee and the flower the flower
Peaks out around 35 years old first test
menstruation around 1516 okay or
whatever and so when you start
menstruating the flower start you know
you get this desire to have a beat but
as you get closer to 35 you reach the
end of your perfect baby-making years it
gets desperate okay and women they were
waiting for a really handsome boyfriend
but they will decide now any boyfriends
okay I gotta have somebody I'm 35 most
women should have a baby before 40 and
this week our desire to have sex so you
can keep more people it it goes like
this in a woman okay at 35 then a lot of
ladies have 35 they are crazy they they
marry somebody they shouldn't marry they
divorce at 40 okay but they just want to
be and they don't understand the earth
they don't understand what's going on
they just want more you
and and they don't understand what's
happening now unfortunately I looked it
up a sperm of a man is active until the
record is 96 okay so a man has the same
strong desire from 16 to 96 okay
the woman peace out and the man is okay
so all men want to have sex they're
watching pornography on the internet
they have to it's their B thing it's not
good by the way
if you can stop it it's good it's like
trying to stop bees and it's very
powerful it's a very very powerful urge
I must have a baby and men will make
babies up to the record is 96 after 40
if a man makes a baby
the chances of birth defect are higher
the sperm starts to the gene ribbon
start to break you start to have
problems with the genetic material so
the men who are most horny is 2530 okay
goes up to 30 something okay they want
to have sex and they run the whole sex
train in the world it's not the Mafia
that makes prostitutes it's not the
Internet companies who make pornography
it's men who wanted I think 12 percent
of all men in the world three and a half
billion people look at pornography once
a month at least once a month okay
a big percent of all boys in the world
whole world go on the internet you know
at least once a month or twice a month
okay one website one the best one I'll
tell you that address later okay just
kidding
why are we talking about all this you
are gonna be an ACI teacher okay and
when you get up to teach there's gonna
be a lot of bees and flowers in the
audience and when you put an available
bee or flower on the stage all the women
respond all the men respond like if you
put a woman on the stage half the men
will fall in love with her okay the good
news is doesn't matter what you look
like okay it just if you're on the stage
they fall in love with the stage not you
okay I told you this story
sometimes I sign a thousand books in one
night and a beautiful woman come down
sit next to me and I sign her book we
take photo like this I try not to sit
too close in case Veronica sees the
photo and then I I want to say hi and
she's already walking away you know so
try to be aware they are not in love
with you
they're in love with the state okay if
if someone else got up and taught the
same class the same girl would fall in
love with that boy it doesn't matter who
gets on the stage
they just need a B and they don't even
know it you see there's an urge inside
of them that wants a B and they they
don't even understand it themselves they
have the desire but they don't know
where it came from and they don't think
about it they just think oh this AC are
teachers they make them more handsome
you know wow I wonder if he has a
girlfriend you know so the purpose of
today's talk is to get used to it and
expect it okay it's a powerful human
force you are not handsome you are not
especially beautiful they're just having
hormones okay and don't fall for it okay
don't don't fall for it now oh she's in
love with me Oh Rajee Guinea came to
bring me hormones you know
countless people have made this mistake
okay and many HCI teachers have failed
and we had to fire them okay because
they date all the girls in the class
they have sex with all the girls in the
class and it's not just boys I mean
women can do the same thing it happened
in ACI classes that many women dated all
the boys in the class
so understand about flowers and bees
okay and when you get up on the stage
and someone falls in love with you
there's a what's his name the ladies in
the rocket rolls concerts they throw
their underwear on the stage like then
it's just B's okay they don't care about
you it's their hormones okay I'm sorry
it's not very romantic of course some
people fall in love that's okay and I
did and and it's gotten a read did for
example and Peter and Marsha did so
there seems to be a difference between
mature love and love for the right
reasons and just hormones okay so I have
to at the end of my talk now I have to
tell you the difference okay and here
are some issues you can think about okay
number one because of your hormones if
two people ask you a question and you're
a man and one is a beautiful young lady
and one is a old lady you will take the
question from the young lady first okay
this is unconscious hormone behavior
okay so you have to be careful and they
say our teacher has to treat all the
students equally okay it doesn't matter
if their hormones are young or hormones
are old or they're an available flower
or they're unavailable flower treat
everybody equally if you find that you
are answering your calling during the
question and answer your call
the young ladies first you have a
hormone problem okay and when you have a
hormone problem it's good to have
another teacher with you okay it's very
good to teach in pairs okay and then
your friend can give you a reality check
you know are you aware you just called
on three pretty girls in a row I don't
know well you did and don't do that so
it's good to have some another person to
teach with you
maybe opposite sex and have a reality
check
okay treat people equally tell your
friend if I don't treat people equally
let me know okay tell me I'm I'm being
I've been hormones are running me okay
all right
discourage inappropriate contact okay
and this depends on every country every
country has different rules about who
you can touch when you can touch in
America I don't know vice-presidents can
kiss ladies hair or not okay there's
rules in each country in when I was in
Mexico I kissed a lady on one cheek and
she got angry at me
she said look are you French we're
Mexican we kiss on both cheeks I'm sorry
I'm sorry I didn't mean to upset you
you know we go we don't go means I I
don't like it right okay well I'm not
gonna tell you about it okay I'm not
gonna get in trouble then it might
happen that someone asked you oh I need
follow-up you know can I have your email
address or WeChat and I
I might need to ask you deeper question
and if you think it's pure then go ahead
it's okay you can share your email or
your WeChat but if you think it's not
pure my suggestion tell them if I'm
teaching with John I'll say you know
John's an expert in that topic you know
you talk to John or you talk to Connie
okay so I'm giving you a real strategy a
real suggestion okay somebody says you
know can I have your email and you think
maybe they just want your power okay
then say you know I'm not very good at
that but my friend isn't really good at
that if they never contact a friend it
means they were having a hormone attack
okay got it okay
so what do I do if I meet someone at a
DC or AC event and I really do like them
like Scott Metairie Peter Marsh I think
I don't know John met Connie in a
retreat you know it's it are we allowed
to date other people is it possible we
have a good relationship yeah but my
suggestion is talk to your partner
teacher and say I'm attracted to this
person I don't have a wife I'm thinking
it might be nice to date them and do
reality check with them okay if you
think you have to check twelve wives in
one year probably it's your hormones
okay no and we don't know we don't
understand the hormone talks to us and
we listen okay we cannot change okay and
and I'm being honest okay and this
caused a lot of trouble also remember if
you say I I want to okay I go to Peter
and say I'm attracted to this girl I'm
not married I would like to ask her out
what do you think as another ACI teacher
that's my partner teacher then you
should say that's fine gisla but meet
their mother first meet their mother
first meet the girl's mother first
because that's what she's gonna look
like later no question always don't be
stupid okay they're not gonna look like
a flower for 50 years okay so fine you
know be honest with yourself meet the
mom and and if you still think that's it
that's a spiritual partner I found my
soul mate then married them okay
then be with them but be honest to
yourself okay
many many marriages fail because the man
lost his hair or the woman got wrinkles
okay and then they don't look like
veggie or guinea anymore
and then they got divorced okay so you
know be honest in your heart marriage is
a lifetime commitment if you choose to
try to find your spouse at an a single
event as a teacher then be honest about
it okay in in in American wedding they
say to love and to cherish through
sickness old age till death do us part
okay even if you get ugly even if you
get old even if I have to wheel you
around the hospital I want to be married
to you okay all right okay
if a CI hears from students and we're
gonna have a secret channel to the ACI
management any one of your students can
complain about you secretly to the home
office okay we're gonna have a
whistleblower channel in English
whistleblower means four or five women
in the group find out the teachers doing
bad things but there's no one to talk to
him so we will have a special email you
don't have to tell us your name
and you can say I think the teacher has
six girlfriends and he has a hormone
problem okay sometimes a student will
write to the whistleblower channel
because they don't like you
not because you're doing anything so the
home office is not stupid I mean we're
kind of stupid but we will check it out
we will check it out okay we won't fire
you as soon as we get a letter well if
we get ten letters I mean the first
letter we will check we will check okay
all right
as a teacher you have to respect other
people's relationships okay in
especially married people people already
in a committed relationship super
careful super careful okay that what's
the general rule yeah pretend they're
wife or husband is there
so would you would you flirt with them
if your partner was there would you
flirt with them if their partner was
there okay so that's a good rule okay
respecting physical boundaries every
country has different boundaries you
know some countries you can hug people
like Mexico I guess you know it's
natural when you meet someone you hug
them
I believe in Asia it's more don't touch
me you know the border is more far each
country has their own custom ACI
teachers teach in many countries
therefore you should learn the customs
where you're teaching okay ask your
friends who are organizing the event is
this a hug country or a high-five
country okay I found after 50 years of
teaching high-five is very safe you know
some lady goes like that I go
you know okay high five is very very
safe
everywhere you go chi-town chi-town
yeah give me five and people like it
it's like American basketball thing and
Chinese like American basketball next
picture I think so this guy's are
shaking
it's a Western guy shaking Asian woman's
hand it may not be appropriate it may be
too far maybe you went across a boundary
in that country you have to learn the
rules you have to learn the rules okay
mmm - law does that mean we should never
act warmly to our students
no you must act warmly to your students
but find out what's the rules in that
country find out what's the boundaries
okay
you should be warm you should be loving
you know I know Scott likes to put his
arm around people like a partner in
America that's very common and it means
you did a good job you pad somebody here
it means you did a good job but make
sure it's okay in that country before
you do it okay otherwise you're gonna
hurt people
next is legal issues okay legal problems
if so I have friends 30 years ago they
started a yoga center it was the biggest
in America and they worked for 30 years
to build the Yoga Center hard hard work
and then one of the teachers had sex
with one of the students actually it was
a woman and a woman and and the woman
sued the yoga studio okay in America
especially I don't know in China what's
a custom but you can have a lawsuit and
they won the lawsuit and they had to
close they actually sold the studio okay
they couldn't stay 30 years of hard work
destroyed in one day by one of the
teachers okay so don't do that to a CI
Tim will have a heart attack he'll have
to find another job
okay and he loves this job and we love
you in the jump so don't forget when you
do this kind of behavior you're risking
legal problems okay you're risking
lawsuit and it's possible a CI will get
sued okay
it's very possible one person who cannot
control their bee pollen can destroy a
CI you can destroy even if the police
don't get you the internet will get you
okay so when you have a big attraction
to somebody try to remember this okay
try to remember that you're hurting all
the other NCI teachers so many people
for 25 years work so hard so much
translation building Diamond Mountain
incredible hard work one be with heavy
hormones can destroy it okay if it gets
on the internet nowadays it's so easy to
get on the Internet okay all right
that's all I have